connectyourcare.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy and End User Terms of Use | ConnectYourCare

Privacy Policy last updated: October 15, 2018

### Financial Notice of Privacy Practices

To read more about our privacy policy as it applies to ConnectYourCare as an IRS-approved non-bank custodian of Health Savings Accounts, please read our [ConnectYourCare Notice of Privacy Practices](https://3yq4681caa0jsu34447gi9n1-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/assets/notice-privacy-practices.pdf).

* * *

### 1\. Privacy Policy

ConnectYourCare recognizes its obligation to protect the personal information you share via this website. We are committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful Internet experience possible.

 **Information Collection and Use**

To conduct our business, we may collect personal information about you from applications or other forms, health plans and providers, your employer and our partners. In some circumstances, you may provide us with additional information yourself. We will not share this information with others using methods different than the methods described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We may use and disclose information collected to affiliated third parties with which we contract for services, including your employer, to administer the program, evaluate and enhance the programs we offer and for certain other purposes as permitted by law. We will use or share only the minimum amount of personal information needed for a particular purpose. These parties are not permitted to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We contractually require affiliated third parties to protect your information. We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties or for reasons unrelated to the servicing of this program. We do not sell or rent any personal information collected whatsoever.

 **Confidentiality**

Our policies limit access to personal user information that is collected from this website to our employees and agents and the employees and/or agents of our affiliates and business partners who need the information to fulfill their business responsibilities. We may disclose personal information collected online to our affiliates and to vendors who assist us with the services. In some cases, this may require your information to be sent to other countries. By supplying your information on this web site, you consent to your information being transferred across international borders to ConnectYourCare and our affiliates, vendors, or agents, unless otherwise agreed to in writing. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements for safeguarding personal information.

Employees and others with duties related to this website must adhere to this Privacy Policy and End User Terms of Use.  Our employees receive annual training about the privacy policies and procedures of ConnectYourCare and its affiliates and subsidiaries. We appreciate that protecting consumer privacy is a key part of our trusted relationship with our clients.

Any employee violating this Privacy Policy and End User Terms of Use may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.

By using this website, you agree that your use of the ConnectYourCare website is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and End User Terms of Use and any applicable agreement you have with ConnectYourCare.

 **Registration**

You must complete a registration to use our website or our mobile application. In order to register you will be required to give personally identifiable information such as date of birth and social security number. We collect this information to verify status and eligibility in order to fulfill claims. ConnectYourCare cannot process your claims or allow access to the secure portion of our website without the registration information.

 **Cookies**

We utilize cookies to facilitate user navigation of our site. A cookie is a small text file containing information about you sent by a web server and stored on your hard drive in your browser. A majority of browsers will allow you to disable cookies or give you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you choose to disable cookies, functionality on the website may be diminished or may not work at all. The use of cookies by third party sites that you may access through a link from our site is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

 **Log Files**

To comply with applicable laws and regulations, we record your IP addresses and login credentials when you access our site. The application logs all transaction-based activity regarding the date, time and user performing the transaction. Furthermore, changes to system configurations are logged for audit and quality control purposes. Our solution supports configurable logging levels.

 **Links to Partner Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. We do not share any information with our partners unless it is necessary for the performance of a service. We cannot guarantee, though, that links to sites we don’t own or control have the same privacy practices, and we cannot assume responsibility for information our partners gather themselves. Be sure to read our partners’ privacy policies once you leave our website.

 **Security Safeguards**

We use extensive physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to make sure your personal information is secure. We restrict access to your personal information to those employees who need to know that information to service this program or to properly conduct our business. All employees are trained on our security and privacy practices. We maintain safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your information.

It is our policy to send and receive personal information through encrypted channels only. All personal data used on this web site is processed using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption.

We will use or share only the minimum amount of personal health information or personally identifiable information needed for a particular purpose. We will continue to limit disclosures of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy even after your relationship with us ends.

 **Communications You May Receive**

We will send you service-related announcements on those occasions when it is necessary to do so. We may contact you to provide information about treatment alternatives or other health-related benefits and services that may be of interest to you. Your employer may opt-out of receiving these types of communications. Please see our opt-out statement below.

 **Opt-in/Opt-out Choices**

The employer has the option to turn on or off communication templates for their participant population as a whole.

Additionally, there are a few communication types that participants may control. For example, participants may elect to receive push notices sent through mobile text messaging. The participant may change these preferences at any time.

We offer three options for receiving participant statements. The employer may choose whether participants receive paper statements, eStatements, or paper statements with eStatements. Employers may also allow participants to choose between paper and eStatements. Participants are automatically enrolled in paper statements but can opt into eStatements online.

 **Surveys**

We request information from users through conducting surveys semiannually. Participation in these surveys is voluntary. Survey information is used for product development and to improve the use and satisfaction of our website.

 **Updating Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you can update personal information that is provided to us by calling _(877) 292-4040_. Your personal information can also be updated through data provided to us from your employer.

 **Data Retention**

We retain personal information necessary to provide you services. If you request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, your employer must contact their designated client services manager, who will coordinate the removal of said data. We will retain and use your personal information as required to fulfill our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Privacy Complaints**

If you feel we are not following state policy, contact customer service at _(877) 292-4040_ , your state or local consumer protection office or the Better Business Bureau.

 **Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. When changes are made to our Privacy Policy, we will post notice of change to our homepage, or other places we deem appropriate. We will also update the Privacy Policy version date located at the top of this Privacy Policy.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/ or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or on our website, as well as for the other reasons herein mentioned.

ConnectYourCare’s data is highly confidential, and therefore data should only be shared with parties external to ConnectYourCare for business purposes. Users must make every reasonable effort to maintain the confidentiality of all ConnectYourCare customer and confidential data. It is against ConnectYourCare policy to disclose any of ConnectYourCare’s customer data without the express prior written consent by the customer. Users must not publicly disclose ConnectYourCare or customer information that may adversely affect ConnectYourCare’s reputation, customer relations, or public image. Finally, ConnectYourCare and its employees will respect and protect the privacy of confidential data in accordance with applicable laws, regulations, and standards.

### 2\. End User Terms of Use

PLEASE READ THESE END USER TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITES, SERVICES, OR MOBILE APPLICATIONS, DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE, SERVICE OR MOBILE APPLICATION IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS.

Last updated: October 4, 2017

These Terms of Use (“Terms”) cover your use and access to our services, mobile application software and websites (“Services”). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your information while our Terms of Use Policy outlines your responsibilities when using our Services. By accessing the Site, Mobile Application and/or using the Services, you agree to abide by these terms of use, including our Privacy Policy (together, “End User Terms”). These End User Terms may be subject to change from time to time, and you are bound by the End User Terms in effect at the time you access the Services. If there is a material change to these End User Terms, we will notify you here by indicating a new effective date at the top of this page. We encourage you to refer to these End User Terms on an ongoing basis.

These End User Terms do not apply to the practices of other websites or companies that ConnectYourCare does not own or control, including but not limited to unaffiliated third party websites, services and applications that you may access through use of the Services (“Third Party Services”). We take no responsibility for the privacy policies or terms of use associated with any Third Party Services and we encourage you to review the applicable terms for each of these sites.

You agree to indemnify, defend and hold ConnectYourCare and its suppliers, affiliates, licensors, and representatives harmless from and against any and all claims, liabilities and other costs arising from: (a) your use or misuse of the Services; (b) your noncompliance with the End User Terms; or (c) any allegation that your use of the Services breaches a third party intellectual property right or is otherwise unlawful.

All trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, and other indicia of origin (collectively, “Marks”) appearing on the Services are the property of ConnectYourCare or ConnectYourCare’s licensors and/or Third party service providers. In using or accessing the Services you agree: (1) not to use the Services or any of the Content contained herein, for any unlawful or fraudulent purpose; (2) not to “spam” others or “phish” for others’ personal information; (3) not to create or use a false identity; (4) not to disrupt or interfere with the security of, attempt to obtain unauthorized access to, or otherwise abuse the Services; (5) not to disrupt or interfere with any other user’s enjoyment of the Services; (6) not to use, frame, or utilize framing techniques to enclose any Marks or other proprietary information (including Content); (7) not to use meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing a Mark; and (8) not to use the Services in a manner that is defamatory, inaccurate, profane, threatening, invasive of a person’s privacy, violative of any third party proprietary rights, or in violation of any law or regulation. In addition, you are prohibited by law, you agree not to reverse engineer or decompile the Services, attempt to do so, or assist anyone in doing so. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify, update, suspend or discontinue the Services at any time without notice.

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, CONNECTYOURCARE AND ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND DISTRIBUTORS MAKE NO WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ABOUT THE SERVICES. THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS.” WE ALSO DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

These End User Terms shall be governed by the laws of the State of Maryland and the United States without regard to conflicts of laws provisions thereof. Any dispute arising from these Terms of Use or the Services shall be resolved in the state or federal courts residing in the Metropolitan Region of Baltimore, Maryland.
